http://meshmountpaper.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected
If you request or submit information to Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape by sending an e-mail via the “mail to:” function or filling out a “request for information” form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape website and not the sites that users access via links from our site. Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies
Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape, please send an e-mail via the feedback form, with “Remove personal information” in the subject line. To update, change, or correct your personal information, please send an e-mail via the feedback form with the appropriate changes.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape and is effective as of November 2008. This statement does not create an agreement between Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
Contact Us Today
Mesh-Mount Paper, Fiberglass & Tape
4 Old Mill Road, Redding, CT 06896 USA
1-877-845-3827
1-203-544-2000
Fax: 203-544-2200
info@meshmountpaper.comSend Page to a Friend
